See you next time.
They're currently inside the courthouse.
We can see that already, fool.
Not as much resistance as I expected.
We should be able to tear right through.
What's that?
Whoa, what?
He's got three heads.
He's just like that dog that guards the underworld.
Marverous?
You mean Cerberus.
Order in the court, damn it.
This is a sacred chamber of law, you hooligans.
Prince, you had that nerve to bust in here, so shut up, sit still and receive your sentence.
All right, guys.
You head to the roof and join up with Straw Hat.
We'll stay here at the door with Yokozuna and hold off the Marines.
We'll watch your back, so keep moving and don't worry about the small prize.
You got it.
Hey, it looks like they're starting some kind of trial over there.
Who cares?
Just ignore them.
Which way do we go?
Straight ahead.
There are stairs on both sides.
Let's make our way to the top.
Right.
Hey!
They're ignoring the trial!
I know they're pirates, but seriously, how rude can these guys get?
Bastards!
How dare you mock the judicial island?
I'll teach you some respect.
Are his sword spinning or am I seeing things?
Charming demon, sleepless night, Unigame!
Is he the guy who broke the door?
Well, that's that.
Now let's get moving!
Right!
He puts all of us to shame, and he's not even the captain of their crew.
Hey, hey, hey!
Wait!
Out of the way, reindeer!
Out of the way, Mosshead!
I'm coming through!
Hmm?
I forgot about him.
Somebody's got to protect Nami from all these bad guys, and that somebody's going to be me,
damn it!
Now move!
Watch it!
What?
Why is he picking a fight now?
If you want to settle this, then bring it!
Shut up!
This is your fault for trying to hog Nami all for yourself!
Follow me, Nami.
Forget about him.
Uh, hey.
We came to this place to rescue Robin, remember?
Oh!
I bet she's waiting for me!
She's waiting for her prince to save her!
She's probably crying right now because she misses me so much!
Whatever!
Ah!
Come on!
Are you kidding me?
Come back, Zoro!
That's the wrong way!
Are you sure?
How can you screw this up when the stairs are right in front of your face?
What's wrong with you?
If you stopped giving such crappy directions, this wouldn't happen!
You are not blaming this on me!
Zoro, I'll try to make you some medicine later to fix your brain problem.
Brain problem?
Hey, Chopper?
Hmm?
Make some for him while you're at it.
I'll try, but he may be beyond help.
I'm starting to have doubts about this whole rescue thing.
They'll pull it together when the going gets tough, I'm sure.
I mean, probably.
I mean, hopefully.
These are serious crimes.
Yes, they're quite grave indeed.
But we should show restraint and sentence them to death!
Agreed!
Are you still with us, Zoro?
It's this way!
Yeah, I know!
Think you can't ignore the Chief Justice, huh?
Chopper, Nami, go on ahead.
I'll make quick work of this thing and catch up with you in a second.
No!
I'm a thing now, am I?
And easy to defeat, no less?
I'll teach you the meaning of fear, you little...
Huh?
Poooooo!
No, stop it!
You gotta go through us first, Cerberus.
Are you sure about this?
Huh.
Ah!
Curse you!
Let's go.
Uh, right.
Gear?
Your techniques have changed?
Are you supposed to be a steam engine?
You certainly are full of hot air.
You're starting to test my patience.
You know...
The truth is...
I'm glad I met you guys when I did.
Because thanks to you, I won't ever lose my friends!
I don't understand.
I think you've got it backwards.
Aren't you going to lose one of your friends precisely because you met us?
The truth is, I'm glad I met you guys when I did.
Because thanks to you, I won't ever lose my friends.
I don't understand. I think you've got it backwards.
Aren't you going to lose one of your friends precisely because you met us?
I knew you were foolish, but now you're just uttering nonsense.
You sure you didn't hate your head?
Gum gum!
Gum!
What? Are you stopping to aim?
That only gives me more time to dodge.
Fine. Let's see how good your aim is then.
Shame!
Shame crystal!
Rifle!
I can't see him at all.
It's spear!
Missile!
Impossible!
No, it has to be.
The truth is, I'm glad I met you guys when I did.
He's using the shave technique.
Only CP9 should know the six powers, but he's clearly mastered it.
Air door!
Huh?
He disappeared.
This is unheard of.
A pirate commanding one of our techniques?
With no training?
Besides that, he can use it so effortlessly.
How is he able to strengthen his body like that?
Is it because of that steam?
This is a sick joke.
Don't tell me, he was capable of this all along.
No, it doesn't matter.
No one can match the speed of a true six powers master.
I won't lose to him!
If I turn his body parts into doors like before, that should stop him dead in his tracks.
After that, all I have to do is finish him off.
Door door!
When we fought before, and it looked like you were disappearing, you were really just moving your feet ten or twenty times a second.
I got the hang of it too, but I never would have figured something like that out on my own.
Like I said, I really am glad I met you guys.
When my friends are in trouble, I'll be able to use your tricks to protect them.
I can take it.
I'll use my strongest defense.
Devine body, strength!
Shedman Zooka!
You sure are tough, aren't you?
All right then.
I was gonna save it, but I have an even better trick.
Don't blink.
I call this...
Man, I'm beat.
Guess my body can't keep this up for long.
Well, I don't care about my body right now.
I need to move ahead.
Dammit!
What's going on here?
Quick!
Fire the cannons, man!
Before they step on us!
Yeah, nice try!
Put those peace shooters on and up to stop me!
You can run!
We'll see you next time.
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'm not coming back!
I don't want to see your faces ever again!
Robin!
Do you hear me?
I just want to die!
Sorry, we're already here and it was a lot of trouble.
So we're gonna go ahead and save you.
On the next One Piece, give us your answer, Robin.
The Straw Hats outcry.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!